I pray to heaven
that my daughter, He Mei,
will return soon.
Great!
Excuse me.
I am He Mei.
Look
how much I resemble my dad.
Follow me, everyone.
I am He Mei.
Where did this clown come from?
You are the 101st person
to impersonate He Mei.
If you were the real He Mei,
the master's lawyer
would have found you
with a paternity test long ago.
Throw her out.
Dad,
I want to be the richest man's daughter.
It seems I shouldn't reveal
my identity so rashly.
I need to get close to him first,
get a hair sample,
and do a DNA test.
Enjoy yourselves, everyone.
Will do.
This way, Master.
Safe travels, Master.
Take care, Master He.
Watch where you're going!
What a waste of my good red wine.
I'm so sorry.
Your clothes are all stained.
Let me wipe it for you.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I was so close.
That damn He Shi.
It wasn't easy getting back
to the He family.
How can I leave so easily?
I have to stay here
until Dad comes back.
Li Zhangxin!
I just
saw you slap He Shi.
I was worried about you,
so I came to check.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
Do you know where the master is going
in such a hurry?
He's probably
going abroad for business.
He's on his way to the airport.
Then he probably won't be back until late.
I mean,
I really like it here.
I majored in nursing in college.
I was wondering
if I could apply to be
the second young master's
personal caregiver.
Since you're pregnant,
it's good to have some help.
Bring your documents tomorrow.
I'll take you to see Mrs. He.
She has the final say
on everything in this manor.
Thank you.
So comfortable.
Zhang Xin,
you've taken over my mother's room
and identity.
You're living quite the life.
Your dream will end soon,
because I'm back.
Mrs. He,
this is Li Zhangxin,
the one I mentioned yesterday
who wants to be
He Yu's personal caregiver.
She majored in nursing in college.
Taking care of He Yu all by myself
is indeed a bit overwhelming right now.
I need a professional to help me.
Hello, Mrs. He.
Here is my resume.
Mrs. He,
Rongcheng University.
A top student, huh?
I won a scholarship every year.
I also graduated at the top of my class.
What are you showing off for?
Fine,
let's do a three-month probation.
No way.
Mrs. He,
this woman
is a temp hired for yesterday's banquet.
She refused to follow my orders.
Instead of working
properly in the kitchen,
she ran around everywhere.
She even slapped the young master.
How can we keep her?
You even dared to hit He Shi.
You settle her in.
Understood, Mrs. He.
I'll get you settled.
The He family has a strict hierarchy.
If you make a mistake here,
no one can save you.
Do you hear me?
Here we are.
This is your room.
Aren't there a few empty rooms?
Why do I have to stay in the storage room?
You're new here.
You have to do as you're told.
Watch your step.
Don't scratch the floor.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
You'll have to pay if you get these dirty.
Fine.
I'm so sorry about that.
You just tripped me.
If I had accidentally
broken something here,
who would take the blame?
Fine.
You've got guts.
Wash all of these clean.
As if I can't deal with you.
Butler Liu,
this is just the beginning.
You've got some nerve
coming here for a job.
You really don't know the rules.
In the He family,
my dad has
the highest status.
Next is
Madam He,
and then me.
At the very bottom
are you servants.
So,
when you see me,
you must greet me.
And
when I talk to you,
you must respond.
Understood, Young Master.
Do you have any other orders?
If not,
please leave.
This is my private space.
Private space?
Everything in the He family is mine,
including you.
So there are
no human rights in the He family.
Your name is Li Zhangxin, right?
I, He Shi, have seen all kinds of women.
Do you really think
you're that charming?
Then what is the Young Master
doing right now?
Let go.
Honey,
Mrs. He wants to see you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You need to be careful of He Shi
in the He family from now on.
He's definitely not a good guy.
Especially a beautiful woman like you,
it's easy to become his prey.
You know what kind of person he is,
so why did you marry him?
For an ordinary girl like me
to marry into the envied He family,
there's naturally a price to pay.
All right.
Then tell me
what I need to pay attention to
when taking care of
the second young master.
Then come with me.
Let me show you around.
Keep the room temperature
between 22 and 26 degrees Celsius
every day.
Turn him over
every two to four hours.
Open the windows for ventilation
for 15 to 30 minutes every day.
Remember to wipe his hands and face
every morning and evening.
And the most important thing...
You just need to talk to him every day.
I'm sure he can hear you.
Thank you for taking care of him.
He's my brother-in-law.
It's the least I can do.
Although he and He Shi are brothers,
their personalities are different.
He Shi is used to being arrogant.
But He Yu is very gentle
and treats everyone well.
Although He Shi and He Yu
are both my brothers,
the only one I truly consider my brother
is He Yu.
Give me back my doll.
What is this ugly thing?
I won't give it back.
I'm going to destroy it.
Brother,
we are Xiaomei's brothers.
We should take up our responsibility
and take good care of her.
She's not my sister.
I don't want you as my big brother.
I want my second brother.
Second brother,
I will do my best to wake you up.
I knew I was right about you.
You've taken great care of He Yu.
I'll get going then.
Second brother.
I'm He Mei.
I'm finally back.
If you could wake up,
you'd definitely recognize me.
Right?
Second brother.
I've missed you so much
all these years.
I really missed you.
Madam He,
I don't think it's appropriate
to let Li Zhangxin take care
of the Second Young Master.
After all, the hit-and-run driver
who struck him
still hasn't been found.
Li Zhangxin
has been scheming
to get close to him.
Who's to say
she isn't the culprit?
If only
she were the killer.
Zhangxin,
it's your first day at work.
Are you tired?
With you here, Madam,
I'm not tired at all.
Don't call me Madam.
I should be older than you.
Just call me Sister Roujing.
Sister Roujing.
Actually,
I had a selfish reason
for asking you to stay.
I don't have many friends here,
and I can't open up to anyone.
My girlfriends
all envy me for marrying
into a wealthy family.
But I care too much about my pride.
How could I tell them
the truth about my life here?
You're quite honest.
You're the same.
From the first time I saw you,
I felt a special connection with you.
Roujing,
I've always been curious about something,
but I don't know if I should ask.
Go ahead.
As long as I can answer it.
That butler is always
sucking up to Mrs. He.
They're both good-looking.
Do they have...
Are you trying to ask
if Mrs. He and the butler
are having an affair?
I'm sorry.
Should I not have asked that?
Let's go.
I'll take you to see.
See what?
I don't think this is a good idea.